const quizDataEsp = [
    {
        question: 'yo | vivir',
        1: 'vivo',
        2: 'viven',
        3: 'vive',
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'nosotras | abrir',
        1: 'abrimos',
        2: 'abren',
        3: 'abrimos',
        correct:3
    },
    {
        question: 'usted | asistir',
        1: 'asisto',
        2: 'asisten',
        3: 'asiste',
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'vosotras | venir',
        1: 'vengo',
        2: 'venís',
        3: 'vienen',
        correct:2
    },
    {
        question: 'tú | sentir',
        1: 'sientes',
        2: 'siente',
        3: 'siento',
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'vosotros | decidir',
        1: 'decido',
        2: 'decidimos',
        3: 'decidís',
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'yo | escribir',
        1: 'escriben',
        2: 'escribo',
        3: 'escribe',
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'yo | salir',
        1: 'salgo',
        2: 'salís',
        3: 'salen',
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'ella | repetir',
        1: 'repite',
        2: 'repetimos',
        3: 'repiten',
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'tú | pedir',
        1: 'pido',
        2: 'pedimos',
        3: 'pides',
        correct: 3
    }
]
